

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

C/C++
C#, Python, Lua, JavaScript and Dart
Visual Studio
Agile
Git
OpenGL
STL containers
Unity
Adobe Photoshop
Office package
3DS Max

## CONTACT

P: +34 634 528 427 E: <u>christt105@gmail.com</u> W: <u>christt105.github.io</u>

#### SOCIAL

Github: christt105

 $Linked In: {\color{blue} \underline{christian martinez delarosa}}$ 

# CHRISTIAN MARTÍNEZ DE LA ROSA

# PROGRAMMER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a programmer who always liked to create games and tools. I started to program four years ago and I have created some games and tools from scratch. I really like to develop tools, as I developed a <u>3D game engine</u> with OpenGL and a Lua scripting system and a <u>3D tile-based map editor</u>.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

UNITY DEVELOPER Learny Land | Feb 2021 - July 2021

• Create apps with Unity for Android and IOS

UNITY 3D/VR DEVELOPER
Nurogames | August 2021 - Present

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN VIDEO GAME DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT CITM-UPC | 2017 - 2021

TECHNOLOGICAL BACCALAURATE
INS Bruguers, Gavà | 2015 - 2017

# AWARDS

Honors in Bachelor subject "Project 2" as a team leader

Honors in Bachelor subject "Artificial Intelligence" as team leader